<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Screen on Error States</title>
    <link>https://errorstates.com/tags/screen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Screen on Error States</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 14:52:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://errorstates.com/tags/screen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>022 - Bank Error</title>
      <link>https://errorstates.com/posts/022-bank-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 14:52:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://errorstates.com/posts/022-bank-error/</guid>
      <description>My wife and I debated for some time as to whether this qualified as an error state. &amp;lsquo;But it&amp;rsquo;s not entirely broken!&amp;rdquo; she argued. &amp;lsquo;But it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;!&amp;rdquo; I countered right back. Not every error state needs to be an example of something visibly broken. There are good error states. That&amp;rsquo;s one of the joys of looking out for them: what does the correct way to engage with someone look like, when the thing itself is out of order? Do you tape a piece of paper? Do you design for the error? 404 and 503 screens on websites are good examples of such recurring problems that most website themes have an explicit design for them. [Continue Reading]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>021 - Starbucks Screens</title>
      <link>https://errorstates.com/posts/021-starbucks-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 14:52:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://errorstates.com/posts/021-starbucks-screens/</guid>
      <description>My last year in high school and a few years through college, I worked at Starbucks. It was a pretty great job as far as customer service went. My town happened to have one of the first Starbucks&amp;rsquo; with a hot-food oven &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; a drive-through.  [Continue Reading]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>020 - Even Geek Squad</title>
      <link>https://errorstates.com/posts/020-even-geek-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 14:51:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://errorstates.com/posts/020-even-geek-squad/</guid>
      <description>Of course, screens break for all sorts of reasons. But like a carpenter with a broken down house or a financial planner constantly on the verge of bankruptcy, it isn&amp;rsquo;t a good sales angle. I&amp;rsquo;m picking on Geek Squad because they&amp;rsquo;re the experts in setting these things up right, housed in one of the only stores that has everything you&amp;rsquo;d need to fix this! [Continue Reading]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>017 - At Ikea</title>
      <link>https://errorstates.com/posts/017-at-ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 12:37:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://errorstates.com/posts/017-at-ikea/</guid>
      <description>Spotted at an Ikea in Denver, Colorado. Coincidentally, there seems to be only one IKEA in Colorado. Whenever a number of different screens come together, there will be some inevitable drift towards being out-of-sync at some point. [Continue Reading]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>004 - User Experience Has Stopped</title>
      <link>https://errorstates.com/posts/004-user-experience-has-stopped/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://errorstates.com/posts/004-user-experience-has-stopped/</guid>
      <description>I went out to a Chinese restaurant with a friend and their back-of-house online order processing setup was in the middle of the hallway, right across from the bathroom. Small New York restaurants, amiright? They had the whole wall covered in different iPads and android tablets. Every company they worked with had a seperate tablet that they needed to manage. My friend &amp;ndash; who had worked at Seamless for a small stretch &amp;ndash; explained that each company tends to send out a free, dedicated (read: locked down) tablet to the restaurants for order processing. [Continue Reading]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>